[lively music playing]
[automated voice] Please take your parking ticket.
Follow the appropriate sign.
[airplane roars overhead]
[horn blares]
[lively music continues]
[machine bleeps]
- Got a delivery. - Perfect, thank you.
- Thanks. - There you go.
[music softens]
[man] Kono! Kono!
Over here, Kono!
Sorry I'm late. Stupid train stalled.
- Is the guest here? - Yeah, standing by.
[lively music continues]
This way. We'll get your makeup done on the move.
- I don't need any. - No, we'll touch you up.
I don't need it. It's already tight with the interview being cut down.
- Whoa! - [postal worker] Oh, so sorry!
[man] Watch where you're going!
Now we'll take a break
and be right back with our weekly check-in with our reporter, Kono.
THESE DAYS WITH KYOKO KONO
One minute to showtime!
There you are! Good morning.
- Sorry to keep you waiting. - I'll take that!
[man breathes heavily]
- Just put some on. - Sure.
- Put some on. - [lively music continues]
[man] Okay, we really need to move. Come on.
[music softens]
- [exhales slowly] - [music fades]
[music resumes]
- [man] Back live in ten seconds! - I've got a package.
[man] Eight, seven,
Six, five, four, three
OPEN IMMEDIATELY
Let's kick off our Friday segment,
Bringing insights from experts across a variety of fields,
Alongside our colleague, Kyoko Kono.
[hosts, together] It's "These Days with Kyoko Kono."
[theme music playing]
[music ends]
Good morning and welcome. I'm Kyoko Kono.
[woman] We'll be on this for 15 minutes.
[Kyoko] you've been hearing the term "biomass power generation" recently.
You might've been wondering, "What is that?"
I'm speaking with someone who can answer that question.
[man] Get the name ready.
He discovered a brand-new method of biomass power generation.
Professor Emeritus Kyugo Sano from Teito University.
- [man] Go to him. - [Kyoko] We appreciate you joining us.
So what is biomass power generation
And why has it been getting so much attention recently
In relation to the environment?
Well, the word "biomass" itself
Was coined from combining the word "bio," meaning biological resources,
And of course "mass", meaning the quantity of those resources.
We're talking about resources that are organic,
From things like plants and animals.
Food waste from our own homes. Sewage from city sewers can also be used.
The options for this waste are endless.
It can be burned directly as fuel or converted into biomass
For power generation.
So it's a way of generating power using the city's waste?
[Sano] Yes, that's exactly what it is.
It's very exciting because, until now,
Disposing of all the city's waste costs an enormous amount of time and money.
But if we were to start using all this waste as fuel,
We could save up to 300 million yen per year, per facility.
- It would be an incredible achievement. - [low, sinister music playing]
[Sano] Now, it wouldn't be without its own set of challenges.
To do it properly, we'd need to establish a collection system
At a local government level,
And that would be for things like food waste and other waste materials.
To be honest, it's far too big a task, so my hope is to draw more attention to it
And eventually the nation at large will recognize its potential.
So it seems like there's still a long way to go then?
Is there a plan in place for when the time comes?
Much of it is still being discussed.
Whoever wants to--
[choking and groaning]
P Professor?
[man] What the hell is going on?
[gurgling and choking]
- What's happening? - Is he choking?
[Sano grunts]
[woman screams]
[gasps]
Cut to commercial, now! Get off this!
[Sano gasping and choking]
[dramatic music playing]
[woman screams]
[sinister music playing]
[woman whimpering]
[screams]
[sinister music continues]
[dark, dramatic music playing]
HUMAN VAPOR
[man 1] Good morning!
- [man 2] Hey, you think you can take off - Hmm. There's eggshell in my soup.
[man 2] Do you know how much of a shit show you caused me?
[man 1] I got into an accident on my bike. I was in the hospital. I left a message.
I could barely walk all week. I'm sorry.
[man 2] Not my problem! You're not getting paid this month.
[man 1] What the hell? That's not fair.
- I didn't plan to get hurt-- - Watch your mouth.
You were scheduled to work and didn't show. That's the bottom line.
Maybe I'll just fire ya.
And you'll go back to your country for being here illegally.
- How do ya like that? - [man 3] Excuse me, sir.
Yeah, what? You got a problem with the food?
No, sir. It's really good.
Good.
[man 3] But the thing is,
I'm not paying for it.
[man 2] Excuse me?
It sounds as though you're not gonna pay this gentleman,
So there's no reason for me to pay either.
[curious music playing]
Palm?
Palm.
Palm!
- [shouts] Palm! - Yes, sir?
[man 2] You know this guy?
No, I don't. Should I, sir?
This doesn't concern you. You'd better stay outta my business.
You're not welcome in my restaurant.
I'm surprised you still have a restaurant.
[man 2] What?
Just by taking a quick look around, you're violating labor laws,
And those ingredients back there are in violation of food sanitation laws.
Not to mention the tables you have outside.
Do you have a permit to put those out there?
[man 2] You have no right to talk to me like that!
Get outta here right now!
[man 4] Whoa, whoa.
[grunts]
[yells]
[man 2 grunting]
- Get off of me, you dick! - [phone vibrating]
[grunting]
Uh, hey, you?
Do you mind, uh, giving me a hand?
- Uh, Palm? It's Palm, right? - [phone vibrating]
- [man 2 grunting] - Palm.
[phone ringing out]
Hey, Okamoto, it's me.
[Okamoto] Chief? What's going on?
- [chief] Where are you right now? - Grabbing some lunch.
- I need you over here right away. - What?
- You remember I'm on suspension, right? - This came from upstairs.
I'm to reinstate you to the First Investigation Division,
effective immediately.
Head to JNT right now.
- Uh, copy that. - [music ends]
Hey, I just wanted to say thank you for what you did in there.
[Okamoto] Ah.
You should probably find somewhere more decent to work.
Yeah, well, no one wants to hire an outsider.
I wouldn't assume that.
But if that's your attitude, nothing's ever gonna change for you.
Hmm.
Best of luck.
- [murmuring] - [officer 1] Get back, please!
[reporter] Let's scrap that piece. This is more important.
[tense string music droning]
[officer 2] You can't go in there. Sir, you need to move.
- [Okamoto] No, it's okay. - [chief] Okamoto.
Took you long enough.
I'm sorry, I got held up.
Your suspension only lasted three months. Gotta say, I'm impressed.
[Okamoto] I am too.
You gonna brief me, or, uh?
Yeah, well
It's a bit of an odd one, to say the least.
[Okamoto] Murder?
[camera clicking]
[Okamoto] What the hell?
What happened here?
Kyugo Sano, Professor of Environmental Engineering,
Was giving an interview when this happened.
What's going on with the smoke?
Oh!
That wasn't all broadcast, was it?
I mean, it was a live interview, so
Jesus Christ.
- Kyoko? - Yeah, I thought you'd notice.
She was the one interviewing Professor Sano
When it all happened.
[Okamoto sighs]
And where is she now?
[chief] Forensics just finished with her. She's in the cafeteria, resting.
Uh-huh.
Do you wanna talk to her?
[chief] Just be careful what you say.
Best to not get too involved with that reporter.
[melancholy music playing]
[officer] Morning, sir.
- Cops everywhere. This is nuts. - My wife is freaking out.
- I wanna get home. - Yeah.
Hi, there. I'm Okamoto from the Metropolitan Police Department.
I was wondering if I could have a few words with Ms. Kono?
[music becomes tense]
[sighs softly]
You okay?
Kenji
You were reinstated.
[sighs] Mm-hmm.
So I guess you're in charge of this case, aren't you?
[Okamoto] Yeah, I guess you could say that, but
As you're aware, it's pretty complex, so it's all hands on deck.
Mm. Of course.
Before the incident,
Was there anything unusual about the Professor or
No, nothing.
You saw the footage.
- [rapid footsteps approaching] - [man] Kyoko!
It's the director.
He's holding an emergency meeting for the chief reporters.
Got it, thanks.
I've told you all I know. May I go now?
Sure.
[Okamoto groans]
I'm guessing you heard that too?
Kono's a chief reporter now, apparently.
So she gets promoted,
And you get the shaft.
Sounds fair, huh?
[Okamoto exhales]
[Okamoto chuckles]
Let's get back to what we're here to do.
[detective] Where do we even start?
[newscaster] We interrupt this program with breaking news.
At roughly 10 a.m. today, live on air,
Professor Emeritus Sano of Teito University
Suffered some sort of unexpected episode and died.
- [man 1] Director! - [director] Hey!
[indistinct chattering]
Hey, good morning.
Apparently, this package arrived just before we went to air.
[intriguing music playing]
Are you gonna open it?
[director] I don't know. Who the hell knows what's in there?
[panicked shouting]
- Kyoko, be careful. - [woman] What if it's a bomb?
[Kyoko scoffs]
- [Kyoko] That's anticlimactic. - Let me see.
Oh. There's a QR code.
That's weird, but okay, I guess we should probably scan it, right?
Before we go scanning random QR codes that could've been sent from terrorists,
Shouldn't we talk to the authorities? Who knows what this is?
Or we just find out right now?
[intriguing music continues]
We won't know either way until we see what it is.
Once we have an idea, we'll make the call, okay?
I got it. I'll put it on the screen.
[man 2] Uh
[music fades out]
[monotone] Hello, everyone.
This message is in regards to the murder that transpired this morning
during JNT's "I Like Mornings" segment.
I orchestrated it.
[tense music playing]
It was 27 years go that I met
the Professor.
That's a very long time.
I can only assume the question that's on all your minds is
why did I decide to kill Professor Sano
and who exactly my next target could be.
He's planning to do more.
[man on video] This video that you're all watching right now
has been sent out to every single major news company
across Tokyo.
Why did I do this?
Because
tomorrow, I would like to hold a press conference.
I will discuss the method of the murder, the reason I did it,
and what I am planning to do next.
The press conference will take place at Bunko Ramen.
I hope to see you there.
4 p.m. sharp.
One last thing.
I will only respond to questions and comments
from the media companies that report this video as their top story.
The choice is yours.
Bye now.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[director] Hmm
So he sent this video to every major media outlet?
Looks like this guy wasn't kidding.
Sakura TV and Ashino Newspaper both got the video too.
Are we sure this is even legit? What if he's just looking for attention?
Is it possible that some random guy
Saw it go down on TV and is screwing with us?
Not possible. Look at the time code.
This video was uploaded just after midnight this morning.
That's before the murder occurred.
There's a good chance this guy was the one behind all this.
Yeah, but that said, are we just gonna stand here
And do whatever this potential psycho wants, really?
Maru TV is about to go live with the video!
ETN too, it's their top story.
Let's broadcast it.
[sighs heavily]
Sir, it's up to you.
Professor Sano's murder happened on our live broadcast this morning
In front of the whole country.
Isn't it our duty to find out why?
[newscaster] Breaking news regarding the murder
Of Professor Kyugo Sano this morning,
That happened during a live interview on this network.
A man claims to be the person responsible.
In the video, the man claims he was the one who orchestrated
the seemingly supernatural attack
- [woman 1] This is nuts. - [man 1] Did you see this?
- [woman 2] The guy died live on air. - [man 2] What's happening?
- [man 3] Why would they even air this? - [student 1] Kana! Kana!
- [student 2] Hello. - [student 1] Did you see this?
It happened on the Friday segment with that reporter.
[student 2] Play it again.
[man] Regarding the murder that happened this morning
WHO IS THE MASTERMIND BEHIND THE INCIDENT?
[man] I planned the whole thing from the start.
Okay, I'm joking, but on today's episode,
I'll be breaking down what the hell happened
and who this mysterious psycho is that can make people float!
That's one hell of a magic trick!
Let's recap. A terrifying man releases a video
claiming he can pop people like balloons!
Pop! Like that!
He says he'll explain the truth tomorrow in a press conference he's hosting
at four at a ramen shop!
[intriguing music playing]
[sighs]
That's just the tip of the iceberg.
There's so much more to this story than meets the eye, folks.
[woman] Give us a hint.
We all wanna know.
[man] Ah. Curious, are you?
I don't blame ya. Well
Other online channels are convinced
That just by talking about this, they'll go viral.
I don't feel that way.
Why not, you ask?
Why do I not live and die by the number of subscribers I have?
'Cause that would be boring.
[pained yelling]
[intriguing music continues]
FUJITA AND KAHO'S TERROR ZONE THANK YOU FOR WATCHING!
[man 1] Where physical evidence is concerned,
No fingerprints other than that of the postal worker were found.
We're also working as fast as we can to identify fingerprints, footprints,
And all other materials found at the scene.
Next, we have a report on this video that's spreading like wildfire
Across all news outlets and social media.
Yes, sir. The video is one minute and 34 seconds long.
We're working around the clock to identify this man,
But so far, we don't have any matches.
Early on in the video,
he claims to have met Professor Sano 27 years ago.
We've been speaking with some of Sano's associates from back then.
However, nothing actionable has come up yet.
So basically,
You know as much now as you did before we got this tape?
That's enough. Let's move on to things we do know.
Yes.
We do have a report on the deceased.
[detective] After examination of the remains recovered at the scene,
It's estimated that the explosion
Most likely started in Professor Sano's lungs.
According to the findings,
The lungs expanded first and then compressed the deceased's neck,
Then exploded with considerable force from the inside.
But hold on now. You can't be serious.
Are you suggesting he swallowed a bomb without even knowing it?
There were no signs of physical explosives.
There were, however, thermal injuries on the inner lung tissue,
More consistent with chemical burns
Than those typically caused by high temperatures.
Are you saying that chemicals were involved here?
More precise analysis is ongoing.
But it does seem to have been caused by some unknown substance.
[man 2] And when can we expect the results of this "more precise analysis"?
The people want an answer!
All right, let's all calm down. We need to stay on point.
The governor's holding a press conference on this tomorrow evening.
We want as much information as possible.
Have we identified the account that posted the video?
About that, sir It routes through multiple overseas servers.
We don't believe it can be traced.
What about this ramen restaurant?
Bunko Ramen is an average ramen restaurant
On Nanahiro Street.
There doesn't seem to be anything noteworthy about it.
It's small, but the area is popular.
[man 3] I want it cornered off
So that it's not a zoo when this guy holds his press conference tomorrow.
[man 4] Yes, sir. We'll get right on it.
- All right, now then-- - [Kenji] Excuse me, sir.
When the governor holds his press conference,
Do you think it would be prudent to maybe warn the people
About the potential risk of a chemical terrorist attack?
After all, the safety of the people is our priority.
Noted. I'll tell the governor.
That's all, thank you.
[officer] Attention!
Salute the superintendent general!
[indistinct chattering]
Okamoto.
Got a sec?
[supt. general groans]
[gentle music playing]
Here.
I know you always forget your pack.
What, did you quit?
[Kenji] It's bad for your health.
Oh, come on now. You're starting to sound like my doctor.
Come on, take it.
[Kenji inhales]
[exhales deeply]
[exhales]
Tell me, you dating anyone new these days?
What? [scoffs] You seriously asking?
Um
There's somebody Chieko wants you to meet, but, uh
What? Are you off the market?
You know how the game is played, Kenji.
You wanna get ahead in this job, you need a good wife.
That's what my father said, before the end.
[supt. general] Smart man.
Hey, weren't you the one who introduced my parents?
Yeah, guilty.
[Kenji] And didn't my mother always hate for you that?
- She sure did. - [Kenji laughs]
Complained about how he never came home.
- [Kenji sniffs] - Yeah.
Being a good cop rarely goes hand in hand with being a good husband and father.
- That's true. - Mm-hmm.
So you
Look like you've gained a few pounds. Those buttons are straining.
Oh
- You think so? - Sorry.
Better not be, with the smoothies I'm drinking every morning.
[laughs] Oh God, smoothies?
Look, I know this is one hell of a case,
But I really think you can crack it. I need you to.
And if there's anything I can do, let me know.
Will do, thanks.
Can I ask you, though
Why this case? You knew I was suspended, right?
Well, that woman,
The one who was there when Sano died
You know, the reporter?
- Kyoko Kono. - She's the reason why.
That woman put you through the wringer, didn't she?
So now you have the opportunity to prove you want nothing to do with her.
That you're over the whole damn thing.
You're welcome.
Okay.
[sighs]
[exhales]
This is, um Sorry, what was it?
My name is Kyoko Kono. I'm from JNT.
Right, yes.
So how can I help you?
It's a request from the PR office. They're looking to do a piece on what we do.
5 YEARS AGO
- It's for Police 24 Hours or something. - Uh-huh.
You're doing a stakeout, right?
Go along with him and feel free to ask whatever you want.
- Hold on, Chief-- - [Kyoko] I appreciate you taking the time.
[Kenji] Uh
Okay.
Well, then
I guess we should go. [clears throat]
[soft music playing]
[soft music continues]
I SAW THE NEWS. WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON?
GET IN TOUCH WHEN YOU CAN?
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY OF CHEMICAL TERRORISM
DON'T COME TO THE SITE TOMORROW! IT'S DANGEROUS
[music fades out]
[airplane whirring overhead]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
- [hushed chattering] - [cameras clicking]
TOKYO METROPOLIS
[man] Good afternoon,
My fellow citizens of Tokyo.
I'm sure that, like myself,
You were all shocked by the events that took place yesterday,
But please rest assured,
The situation is under complete control.
The Tokyo Metropolitan Government has full confidence in our police department.
Their top priority is your safety.
Right now, they are dedicating all their time and resources
To getting to the bottom of what transpired yesterday.
The police department felt it appropriate
To warn you all of the possibility of a chemical terrorist attack.
It is for that reason that we have requested
The immediate assistance of the riot police
At the location of the suspect's press conference.
My plea to the media,
Keep away from the location of the press conference.
- Do not go near this location. - [climactic music playing]
- We cannot guarantee your safety. - [car horn beeps]
- Regarding the man in the video - [horn beeps]
[sighs] Really doesn't seem like anyone's listening to Governor Miura now, does it?
- [horn beeps] - [press conference continues on radio]
[detective] Get outta the way, lady, or you'll get my bumper in your ass.
- [officer 1] Car coming. Make room. - [officer 2] Move! Step back.
[detective chuckles]
It was a joke, calm down.
- [officer 3] Outta the way! - [officer 4] Ma'am, get back! Move!
[officer 5] Stand aside, right there. Car coming through, make way!
- Out of their way! - [horn beeps]
[officer 6] Please move now! If you don't move, we'll detain you.
[climactic music continues]
[helicopter whirring overhead]
[music ends]
[indistinct chattering outside]
[mysterious music playing]
[sniffs]
- Check that out. - [detective] Got it.
[mysterious music continues]
[sighs]
[indistinct chattering outside]
[soft music playing]
[radio DJ] Good evening, night owls
[Kenji] To be honest, these stakeouts are a waste of time,
So get some sleep if you're tired.
I'm fine, thanks.
I, uh
Have insomnia anyway.
So
It's not like I would be able to sleep.
I'm used to staying up late.
I heard something interesting.
When you can't sleep,
Just put your hand on your chest like this.
You'll feel the rhythm of your heartbeat and it calms you down.
- Is that actually a thing? - Yeah.
I'm serious. Go on, try it.
[DJ continues talking on radio]
Close your eyes too.
[Kyoko breathes slowly]
["Ellie My Love" by Southern All Stars playing on radio]
See?
Don't you feel relaxed?
I don't know
[chuckles]
Um yeah.
Worth a shot.
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
[Kenji hums along softly]
What do you think of it?
This song.
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
My dad liked it.
[lyrics in Japanese]
What about you?
♪ On my mind ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
Actually
It's the same for me.
Hmm.
♪ Ellie, my love ♪
[thunder rumbles]
[soft music playing]
[truck horn beeps]
[soft music continues]
- [indistinct chattering] - [horns beeping]
[woman] Sorry, yeah, just through here. Excuse me, sorry. Thank you.
[sighs]
[detective] Just did a sweep, nothing unusual.
[Kenji] Okay.
Do you think he's really gonna show?
Almost time, it's 3:50.
[Kyoko inhales sharply]
Another ten minutes.
All we can do is wait.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, it's Nishiyama from Social Affairs. We're about ready to broadcast.
Okay. Yeah, please do.
[detective] He's 25 minutes late now.
I think the bastard was bluffing.
Well, would you just show up to this shit show if you were him?
You're basically asking to get arrested.
This is all part of some master plan. Must be.
[owner] How long is this gonna take, huh?
I'm closing my business for this?! What the hell is going on?
Whoever this asshole is, he's not coming, hate to break it to you!
I better be compensated for the business I'm losing!
- Jesus. - [owner] How long are we waiting?
- You think this guy's just gonna roll in - The owner's having a total freak out.
- Tatsuya, wait here. - [owner] This is crazy!
- Where you going? - [woman] Hey.
[Tatsuya] Whoa, hold on. You can't just run off like that.
Dammit!
- Such bullshit! - [Kyoko] Uh
Hey, excuse me.
Oh
- I know you, don't I? - Oh, um, yes.
I'm Kyoko Kono. You might know me from JNT.
Oh yeah, you were there when, um, that person exploded.
- That was you! - Yeah, that was me.
Thank you.
Even after something traumatic like that,
We're supposed to get back out here as though it were nothing.
It's gotta be a tough job. My job's pretty hard too, you know?
You should see all the crap I have to deal with here!
Mondays Mondays, I do a deep clean. I should've done that last night, huh?
Yeah, listen
Have you always run the business here?
Huh?
- [woman 1] Is this guy even coming? - [woman 2] He fooled us. Bastard.
- [woman 3] Huh? - [woman 4] Let's get outta here.
- [man] I left work early for this. - [woman 5] Let's go.
[phone buzzes]
KYOKO KONO 1 MESSAGE
[sighs]
BUNKO RAMEN USED TO BE IN A DIFFERENT LOCATION
[suspenseful music building]
Let's go.
- [Tatsuya] Okay, this is it. - [suspenseful music continues]
[Tatsuya] Hey, hold up.
Kyoko!
Hang on a second!
BUNKO RAMEN
Jesus.
- [music becomes unsettling] - [rat squeaks]
[mysterious music playing]
[Tatsuya] Could you please wait a second?
You can't just walk in somewhere without asking
Wow!
[mysterious music intensifies]
[newscaster] The very reporter who witnessed the murder
is about to go live with the man claiming to be the perpetrator.
[Kyoko] I'm currently sitting for an exclusive interview
with the man claiming to be behind yesterday's on-air murder.
[mysterious music continues]
[music fades]
[Kyoko] Thank you for agreeing to this. Could you introduce yourself?
[monotone] I am someone who's been the victim of terrible suffering.
So,
Was Professor Sano the cause of this suffering?
Did you do this out of revenge?
Yes.
Professor Sano was murdered due to the many crimes he committed.
Could you tell us what he did?
What were these alleged crimes, exactly?
White.
Center.
Sorry? White Center?
Could you tell us what that is?
You wouldn't know about it.
It was a very long time ago.
The people who were involved with White Center
Must be remembering the crimes they committed
And panicking as they watch this.
And who are these people you're talking about?
[man] They are the ones who control this society.
No matter what I say here and now or how much proof I have,
They'll use their power to cover up their crimes.
JNT REPORTER'S EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
MAN WHO SAYS HE KILLED PROF. SANO
This is my solemn vow to all those guilty souls watching this.
I'm going to kill you all
One by one.
But what if they apologize?
Admit to their wrongdoings, make amends in some way.
Maybe you could still reconcile this without more bloodshed.
[man] It's possible,
But I highly doubt these people would ever apologize.
[sirens wailing]
It seems like this is the end of our interview.
[officers shouting outside]
Wait, hold on!
Can you tell us your name?
[low, tense music playing]
From now on, they will call me
The Human Vapor.
I I don't understand.
[sinister music playing]
Hey, freeze!
Hands where I can see them!
Now!
Go on.
[sinister music playing]
[erratic hissing and sizzling]
[concerned murmuring]
[glass cracking]
[shouting and screaming]
[officers groaning and coughing]
[sinister music continues]
[Kenji] You all right?
[gas hissing]
[whooshing]
[whooshing fades]
[officer 1 grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[officer 2 yelps]
[officers grunting and groaning]
[officers shouting]
[panicked chattering]
[dramatic music continues]
[officers shouting]
[officers yelling]
[officers scream]
[dramatic, eerie music playing]
[whooshing]
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[music ends]
[Human Vapor] The people involved with White Center
must be remembering the crimes they committed
and panicking as they watch this now.
This is my solemn vow to all guilty parties
MAN CALLING HIMSELF THE HUMAN VAPOR
I'm going to kill all of you,
one by one.
[foreboding music playing]
[exhales heavily]
[dramatic orchestral music playing]